Guide to the Protestant Episcopal Bishops Collection
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Correspondence, Series I
  - American Bishops
    - Williams, John, 1817-1899 (Conn.)
      - Miscellaneous documents; memorial (9), 1835, 1865, 1879, undated (Box 11, Folder 422)
    - Wilmer, Joseph Pere Bell 1812-1878 (5), 1859, 1875, 1878 (Box 12, Folder 423)
    - Wilmer, Richard Hooker 1816-1900, (Ala.) (9), 1874, 1898-1894, 1898, 1900 (Box 12, Folder 424)
    - Wilner, Robert Franklin 1889-, (Phillippines) (3), 1938 (Box 12, Folder 425)
    - Wilson, Frank Elmer 1885-, (Eau Claire, Wisc.) (4), 1935, 1937, 1941, undated (Box 12, Folder 426)
    - Winchester, James Ridout 1852-1914 (Ark.) (9), 1911-1912, 1916-1917, 1937, undated (Box 12, Folder 427)
    - Wing, John Durham 1882-, (S. Fla.) (4), 1933, 1936-1937 (Box 12, Folder 428)
    - Wingfield, John Henry Ducachet 1833-1898, (N. Cal.) (7), 1860, 1885, 1890, 1894 (Box 12, Folder 429)
    - Wise, James 1875-, (Kan.) (5), 1918, 1820, 1836-1837 (Box 12, Folder 430)
    - Woodcock, Charles Edward 1854-1940, (KY.) (13), 1904-1906, 1908, 1913, 1918, 1922, 1927-1928 (Box 12, Folder 431)
    - Worthington, George 1840-1908, (Neb.) (9), 1880, 1891, 1901, 1903-1904, undated (Box 12, Folder 432)
    - Young, John Freeman 1820-1885, (Fla.) (4), 1873, 1881, 1883, undated (Box 12, Folder 433)
    - Ziegler, Winfred Hamlin 1885-, (Wy.) (1), 1937 (Box 12, Folder 434)
  - Non-American Bishops
    - Auckland, Robert John Eden 1799-1870, (Bath and Wells) (1), undated (Box 12, Folder 435)
    - Barton, Arthur William (Kilmore, Ireland) (2), 1934 (Box 12, Folder 436)
      [1 from Chorley, 1934]
    - Burroughs, Edward Arthur 1882-, (Ripon, England) (1), 1930 (Box 12, Folder 437)
    - Darbyshire, John Russell 1880-, (Glasgow & Galloway; Capetown) (1), 1934 (Box 12, Folder 438)
    - Dauglisch, John 1879-, (Nassau) (1), 1938 (Box 12, Folder 439)
    - Day, John Godfrey Fitzmaurice 1874- (Kilkenny [Ossory]) (1), 1934 (Box 12, Folder 440)
    - Deane, Frederic Llewelyn 1868-, (Aberdeen & Orkney) (14), 1934-1935 (Box 12, Folder 441)
    - Dunn, Edward Arthur 1870-, (Honduras) (1), 1921 (Box 12, Folder 442)
    - Herzog, Eduard (Vevey, Switz.?) (3), 1882, 1884-1885 (Box 12, Folder 443)
    - Holmes, William Hardy 1873-, (Tuam, Ireland) (1), 1934 (Box 12, Folder 444)
    - Ingram, Arthur Foley Winnington 1858-, (London) (1), 1934 (Box 12, Folder 445)
    - Kennion, George Wyndham 1845-, (Bath & Wells) (1), 1915 (Box 12, Folder 446)
    - King, George Lanchester 1860-, (Madagascar) (1), 1923 (Box 12, Folder 447)
    - Knight, Arthur Mesac 1864-1939, (Canterbury) (1), 1918 (Box 12, Folder 448)
    - Lang, Cosmo Gordon 1864-, (Canterbury) (2), 1923 (Box 12, Folder 449)
    - McCarthy, Edward Joseph 1850-1931, (Halifax, N.S.) (1), 1922 (Box 12, Folder 450)
    - Maclean, Arthur John 1858-, (Moray, Scotland) (2), 1915, 1934 (Box 12, Folder 451)
    - Macmanaway, James (Clogher, Ireland) (1), 1934 (Box 12, Folder 452)
    - Matheson, Samuel Pritchard 1852-, (Rupert's Land, Canada) (1), 1921 (Box 12, Folder 453)
    - Montgomery, Henry Hutchinson 1847-, (Tasmania) (1), 1906 (Box 12, Folder 454)
    - Peacocke, Joseph Irvine 1866-, (Derry & Raphoe, Ireland) (1), 1934 (Box 12, Folder 455)
    - Reinkens, Joseph Hubert 1821-1896, (Bonn?) (2), 1879, 1883 (Box 12, Folder 456)
    - Robberds, Walter John Forbes 1863-, (Brechin, Scotland) (1), 1934 (Box 12, Folder 457)
    - Soderblom, Nathan [Lars Olaf Jonathan] 1866-, (Usala?) (1), 1923 (Box 12, Folder 458)
    - Sweeney, James Fielding 1857-, (Toronto) (1), 1921 (Box 12, Folder 459)
    - Temple, William 1881-1944, (Canterbury) (1), 1934 (Box 12, Folder 460)
    - Tozer, William George (Cen. Africa) (2), 1876 (Box 12, Folder 461)
    - Venables, Addington Robert Peel (Nassau) (1), 1867 (Box 12, Folder 462)
    - Walpole, George Henry Somerset 1854-1929, (Edinburgh) (1), 1915 (Box 12, Folder 463)
    - Warner, Kenneth Charles Harman 1891-, (Edinburgh) (1), 1934 (Box 12, Folder 464)
    - White, Henry Vere 1853-, (Limerick, Ireland) (1), 1934 (Box 12, Folder 465)
    - Williams, David 1859-1931, (Huron, Canada) (1), 1916 (Box 12, Folder 466)
  - Non-Bishop Letters
    [all but two to M.L. Woolsey]
- Subject File, Series II
  - American Bishops
    - Autographs and photographs, 1884-1900 (Box 12, Folder 468)
    - Table: The Succession of American Bishops (Nos. 1-396), 1936 (Box 13, Folder 469)
    - Ely, Foster: Journal of letters received (Nos. 1-264), 1914 (Box 13, Folder 470)
    - Ely, Foster: Original index of letters compiled and presented to Berkeley Divinity School, including the school's certificate of receipt, 1908-1909, 1914 (Box 13, Folder 471)
  - Non-American Bishops
    - Autographs (34), 1898 (Box 13, Folder 472)
    - Pictures from magazines (17), 1929, 1937, 1949, undated (Box 13, Folder 473)
    - Response to American request for Episcopal status, 1786, signed by 19 English Bishops (Box 13, Folder 474)
  - Trinity Church, New Haven
    - Lease agreements with John and Fanny Scott, 1814, 1847 (Box 13, Folder 475)
    - Lease renewal with John Scott, Jr., 1860 (Box 13, Folder 476)
    - Lease renewals with Mary A. Scott, 1867, 1874, 1881 (Box 13, Folder 477)
    - Reuben Sherwood documents
      - Appointment as lay reader by Bp. Jn. Croes, 1814 (Box 13, Folder 478)
      - Ordination as deacon by Bp. Alexander Griswold, 1815 (Box 13, Folder 479)
      - Priestly ordination by Bp. John H. Hobart, 1819 (Box 13, Folder 480)
      - Commission as priest in Norwalk by Bp. Thomas C. Brownell, 1819 (Box 13, Folder 481)
    - Original draft of cornerstone inscription, 1831 (Box 13, Folder 482)
    - Records of the Sunday School Teachers Society, 1830-1840 (Box 13, Folder 483)
  - St. Bartholomew's Church, New York
    - The Centennial History of Saint Bartholomew's Church by E. Clowes Chorley, 1935 (Box 13, Folder 484)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 13, Folder 485)